Guide to the Myles Glasgow papers, 1967-1998 MS2155
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Myles Glasgow papers
1967-1998
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Glasgow, Myles
MS2155
1.5 Linear Feet
Collection contains correspondence, reports, notes, photographs, and transcripts from 1967-1998 relating to the civic work of Myles Glasgow and covers such topics as zoning, bridge safety, Adams Morgan, and transportation.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Collection donated by Myles Glasgow.
Historical or Biographical Note
Myles Glasgow is an attorney in Washington, D.C. He was director of University Legal Services, a nonproft organization that represents tenants in landlord-tenant disputes.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains correspondence, reports, notes, photographs, and transcripts. The material covers the dates 1967-98. This material relates to the civic work of Myles Glasgow and covers such topics as zoning, bridge safety, Adams Morgan, and transportation.
Photographs; Transportation; Zoning; Bridges; Adams Morgan (Washington, D.C.); Washington (D.C.); Glasgow, Myles
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: White House, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Witness Protection, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Washington Post, 1990-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: U.S. Congress' Balanced Budget in 1995, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Unabomber, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Caroll Sockwell, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Taxicab, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Smithsonian Parking, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Supreme Court, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Social Programs, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Property Taxes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Philadelphia, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Personal on Poetics Thoughts, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Personal Injury Recovery Limits, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Lieutenant Kelly, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Letters to the Editor of SPD: Judges, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Israel, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: International Issues, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Gambling, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: D.C. Schools, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: D.C. Leadership Problems, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Letters to the Editor: D.C. and Barry, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Board of Election, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Dave Clarke, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Cuba, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Adams Morgan ANC, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Dr. Blyn Re: Jose Luis, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Arnebeck, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Letters to the Editor: DC City Council, 1992-1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Letters to the Editor or SPD: Miscellaneous, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- National Speech/Language Therapy Center Letter, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Briefing Book: Duke Ellington Memorial Bridge Safety Fences, 03/04/1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Bridge ANC Statements, 1985-1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Bridge ANC Statements, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Eileen Crawford Written Complaint, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Letter to Julian Dixon, 06/16/1990 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Duke Ellington Bridge, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Duke Ellington Bridge: Fence Removal, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Duke Ellington Bridge, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Duke Ellington Bridge: Draft and Memos, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Duke Ellington Bridge: Statement and Groups, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Bridge Data Re: Fences and Suicides, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Duke Ellington Bridge, 1983-1990 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Ellington Bridge Fence/ Myles Glasgow, 03/16/1990 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Adams Morgan: Democratic Action to Save a Neighborhood Report, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Pamphlets, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Photograph of Man, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Reed-Cooke Rezoning, 1970-1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Rezoning Miscellaneous, 1967-1986 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Photograph of two children, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Transcript of Proceedings: D.C. Zoning Commission Public Hearing, 10/20/1986 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Transcript of Proceedings: D.C. Zoning Commission Public Hearing, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Washington Convention Center FY 95 Responses, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Miscellaneous, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Take or Pay Legal Research: Letters to School Board and Control Board, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Take or Pay Legal Research: Letters to School Board and Control Board, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Take or Pay Legal Research: Letters to School Board and Control Board, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Poster: Freeway Cancer Hits DC, 01/1970 (Map-folder 1, Item 1)
- Poster: White Men's Roads Thru Black Men's Homes!, undated (Map-folder 1, Item 2)